[
    {
        "question":"What is Sets?",
        "option1":"Collection Of Things",
        "option2":"Chitwan",
        "option3":"Film",
        "answer":"1"
    },
        {
        "question":"14/24 =...",
        "option1":"1/2",
        "option2":"4/4",
        "option3":"7/12",
        "answer":"3"
    },
        {
        "question":"Root of 9..",
        "option1":"1",
        "option2":"2",
        "option3":"3",
        "answer":"3"
    },
        {
        "question":"cp=Rs.20 , sp= Rs.90, . P=?",
        "option1":"Rs.7",
        "option2":"Rs. 70",
        "option3":"Rs. 700",
        "answer":"2"
    },
        {
        "question":"Coefficient 3, base X, Power 4 is ..",
        "option1":"X",
        "option2":"3X",
        "option3":"3X⁴",
        "answer":"3"
    },
        {
        "question":"2(4-6+7)=",
        "option1":"1",
        "option2":"10",
        "option3":"100",
        "answer":"2"
    },
        {
        "question":"10:45 = ",
        "option1":"1:4",
        "option2":"2:9",
        "option3":"4:2",
        "answer":"2"
    },
        {
        "question":"7²",
        "option1":"14",
        "option2":"48",
        "option3":"49",
        "answer":"3"
    },
        {
        "question":"2x3x4x5",
        "option1":"1",
        "option2":"12",
        "option3":"120",
        "answer":"3"
    },
        {
        "question":"8+(6+4)-{4x6-4}",
        "option1":"2",
        "option2":"-2",
        "option3":"20",
        "answer":"2"
    },
        {
        "question":"The Difference Of 4 and 8 is ..",
        "option1":"4",
        "option2":"8",
        "option3":"10",
        "answer":"1"
    }
    ]